<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="h36cd182ag0539g4c07g9733g9800e2be2e61" version="1">Profane Soul</content>
	<content contentuid="hfbd01de7g915eg4e1bga526gbf3a598c1162" version="1">Blood hunters belonging to the Order of the Profane Soul have pushed the limits of hemocraft for use against some of the most terrifying creatures corrupting the world. Though they might have traded a part of themselves for their power, the members of this order know the benefits of that power far outweigh the price.</content>
	<content contentuid="h92dc4da9gf353g4baegbae1ge71394d69275" version="1">Great Old Ones</content>
	<content contentuid="heabafd41g22dcg4cb6g82c6g89fdf8030409" version="1">Your patron is a mysterious entity whose nature is utterly foreign to the fabric of reality.</content>
	<content contentuid="hff4a8cf6g77feg403dgbdddg0d207660d5e8" version="1">Rite Focus</content>
	<content contentuid="hca47f128g1d44g46c7g9b2bg1fe3ad4761d6" version="1">The Great Old One. When you score a critical hit against a creature, that creature and any other creatures of your choice within 10 feet of it are frightened of you until the end of your next turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="hdecd76feg3b78g4f4ag91a8g113f5b03fbb8" version="1">Revealed Arcana</content>
	<content contentuid="ha10be3d7g817bg4683g8304g4d3b107742e5" version="1">At 7th level, your patron grants you the use of a distinctive spell based on your pact. You cast this spell using any pact magic spell slot, and can’t do so again until you finish a long rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1e5f0864f08844d1a0246eca13c199c7dfce" version="1">Improved War Magic</content>
	<content contentuid="h8432f553139941acacbb6f0c58e36a26425b" version="1">When you use your action to cast a spell, you can make one weapon attack as a bonus action. </content>
    <content contentuid="hb56e10788bbf4426a0efb802ef4b9763e229" version="1">Hardened Soul</content>
	<content contentuid="h66a0b78d966640a08a64f7d67e61fc7ccgg5" version="1">When you reach 14th level, you have advantage on saving throws against being charmed and frightened.</content>
    <content contentuid="h54824ff5b0b94187894160fd5d8f5478c4g9" version="1">Unsealed Arcana</content>
	<content contentuid="hfce2b19cef9c46e68615ed4c5b78339dda13" version="1">At 15th level, your patron grants you the use of an additional spell based on your pact. You cast this spell without expending a spell slot, and can’t do so again until you finish a long rest.</content>
</contentList>